What’s new in Foxit Reader 1.1
======================================================================================================================
New features:

1. Cloud-based shared reviews

Read, reply, and share comments in the cloud for effective collaboration with team members. (Foxit PhantomPDF Business is required to initiate a cloud-based shared review, but Foxit Reader users can participate in the reviews). 

2. Add and open file attachments 

Open and view attachments embedded in PDF files, and attach files to PDF files for quick and easy reference.

3. Drawing markup tools

Help users add lines, ovals, rectangles, and arrows to PDF files, making it easy to provide visual feedback on PDF documents during reading and reviewing. 

Improvements:

1. Optimized installation package for streamlined workflow. 

2. Support for installing Foxit Reader using a command line. 



What’s New in Foxit Reader 1.0.1
======================================================================================================================
Fixed some issues to improve the user experience. 



What’s New in Foxit Reader 1.0
======================================================================================================================
New Features:

1. Flexible Document Views

Supports multi-tab document view and flexible page display modes to deliver a better reading experience.

2. PDF Navigation by Page Number, Page Thumbnail, or Bookmark

Allows you to easily and quickly jump to a certain page or a specific chapter by Page Number, Page Thumbnail, or Bookmark.

3. Text Search 

Supports searching text to find specific information in PDF files. 

4. Add Comments with Feature Rich Comment Tools

Provides feature rich comment tools to help you add text markups, freeform drawings, lines of text, and note comments in PDF files with ease.

5. Microsoft® RMS Integration

Allows you to decrypt and encrypt Microsoft Active Directory® or Azure Rights Management Services protected PDF files through the optional Foxit RMS Plug-in.

6. Security Watermarks

Enables you to add static or dynamic security watermarks in PDF files to prevent the unintentional distribution of sensitive materials.


Download the Latest Version
========================================================================================================================
You can download the latest version of Foxit Reader from our website at www.foxitsoftware.com.



Contact Us
======================================================================================================================
If you have any questions using Foxit Reader, please contact us by email:

Sales and Information - sales@foxitsoftware.com
Marketing Service - marketing@foxitsoftware.com
Technical Support - support@foxitsoftware.com
Website Questions - webmaster@foxitsoftware.com



Foxit Software Incorporated

Address: 42840 Christy Street. Suite 201, Fremont CA 94538, USA

Sales Phone: 1-866-680-3668 (24/7)

Support Phone: 1-866-MYFOXIT or 1-866-693-6948(24/7)

Fax: 510-405-9288

Web: www.foxitsoftware.com
